Guide to the Washington Area Music Association records, 1984-2016 MS2331
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Artist/Band Promotional materials, 1985-2009; Series 6; 2.5 Linear Feet
  - Kid Creole and the Coconuts (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - Killgo, Kieth, 1996 (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - Letters and Notes (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - Landon, Katrina, 1998 (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - Lee, Tracy (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Little Red and the Renegades, 1992 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - The Lisa Cerbone Band (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Liz Meyers and Friends (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Louie and the Creole Man (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Love Riot, 1997 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Magnet (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Maitland, Alan (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Mary Pat Hughes' 2 Funkin' Heavy (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Mary's Suicide, 1991 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Mahdi Mob, 1991 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Major and Rathell, 1994 (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Manifesto (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Media Kit, 1998 (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - McCabe, Rebecca (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - Pat McGee Band, 1997 (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - McLoed, Zan, 1993 (Box 56, Folder 17)
  - The Michael Sheppard Group (Box 56, Folder 18)
  - Minibar, 2001 (Box 56, Folder 19)
  - Morra, Joe (Box 56, Folder 20)
  - Mullet Record Internatinonal, 1998 (Box 56, Folder 21)
  - Murphey, Luci (Box 56, Folder 22)
  - No Description Given (Box 56, Folder 23)
  - Nonchalent (Box 56, Folder 24)
  - The Nighthawks, 1995 (Box 56, Folder 25)
  - Nina Story and the Lost Generation (Box 56, Folder 26)
  - Oasis, 1998 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - One Man Gang (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - The Orioles (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Parker, Bobby (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Parsons, Bill, 1995 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Peaches and Herb (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - The Pietasters, 1997 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Phillips, Mark (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - The Plunge, 1998 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Poole (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Power of Three, 1997 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Pra sada-Rao, Tom, 1994 (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Project One (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Puddle Duck (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Relativity, 1995 (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - The Revellaires (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - Richards, Sue (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Ripsaw, 1989 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - River (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - The Road (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Rollins (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Royal Trux (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Ruthie and the Wranglers, 1997 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Saffire (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Section 8 Mob, 1993 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Sev (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Sharp, David, 1993 (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Shai (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Sky and Telescope, 1989 (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - Slice of Life (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - Smith, Debbie (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - Smith, Jeffrey (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - Sound of Apryl (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - Spencer, Jon (Box 58, Folder 18)
  - Strumpt, Lois (Box 58, Folder 19)
  - Stagger Stagger Crawl (Box 58, Folder 20)
  - Starburst (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Starpoint (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Steer, Glem, 1995 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Steeleye Spam (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Stevens, Ben, 1997 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Stone, Cornell (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Susi Beauty, 1990 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - The Sugarvals (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Taylor, Virgil (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Ten-Thirty, 1989 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Terry, Tony (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Thackery, Jimmy (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Three Percent Fat (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Tice, Jackie, 1998 (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - Tittley, Simon, 1993 (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - Tony, Kevin (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - Tucker, Leslie (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - Turner, Nap (Box 59, Folder 18)
  - Tuscadero (Box 59, Folder 19)
  - Unrest! (Box 59, Folder 20)
  - Unorthodox (Box 59, Folder 21)
  - Vann, Eddie (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Velocity Girl (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Verborgen, 1998 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Waldo (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Walker, Melissa (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Watkins, Kit, 2009 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Wax (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Walker, Jan (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Waters, Crystal (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Willie Jolley (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - The Winstons (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Wretched (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - Wyzard (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - XL (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - Y-not (Box 60, Folder 15)
  - The Zimmermans (Box 60, Folder 16)
  - Zoothead (Box 60, Folder 17)
  - Misc. (Box 60, Folder 18)
- Published materials, 1985-2016; Series 7; 4 Linear Feet
  This series is comprised of newspapers, magazines, online articles, programs, and event handouts relating to the WAMA organization.
  Arranged in loose chornological order.
  - Printed Online Articles, 1998-2009 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Printed Online Articles, 1998-2009 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - WAMA news, 1989-1991 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - WAMA news, 1992-1994 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Magazines, 1985-2001 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Newspaper Cutouts, 1989-1992 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - WAMA news, 1994-1997 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - WAMA news, 1998-2003 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Wammies/Crosstown Programs, 1987-2007 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Event Handouts, 2003-2016 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Wammies Magazines, 1986-1992 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Wammies Magazines, 1993-2003 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Wammies Magazines, 2004-2008 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Wammies Magazines, 2009-2011 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Wammies Magazines, 2012-2016 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - WAMA Pages, 1991-1999 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - WAMA Pages, 1998-2012 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Newspapers, 1990-1998 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Newspapers, 1990-1998 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Newspapers, 1993-1994 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Wammies Magazines, 1985 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Crosstown Jams Poster, 2005 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Newspapers, 1990-1994 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Newspapers (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Newspapers, 1988-1997 (Box 66, Folder 4)
- Photographs and posters, undated; Series 8; .5 Linear Feet
  The series contains photographs and prints related primarily to the WAMA organization and its members.
  This series is arranged in the order that was held within WAMA original records.
  - Wammies Photos, 2001 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Promotional Artist/Band Images (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Promotional Artist/Band Images (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Promotional Artist/Band Images (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Promotional Artist/Band Images (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Promotional Artist/Band Images (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Promotional Artist/Band Images (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Promotional Artist/Band Images (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Promotional Artist/Band Images (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Promotional Artist/Band Images (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Promotional Artist/Band Images (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Posters, Circa 1970-2000; Series 8 (Map-folder 1)